Sarah Stockil

123 Main Street, Reno, NV45678 sarah.stockil@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

Goal-orientated retail store manager with over 10 years of experience. Well versed in all aspects of running a successful retail store, including merchandising, opening and closing procedures, recruiting, and banking. Proven track record in motivating employees to meet performance goals and work together as a team.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Retail Management

Nevada University, Reno, NV September 2006 - July 2010

Key Skills

- Natural leader
- Team building
- Good communication skills
- Motivator
- Inventory Management
- Commercial Awareness
- Employee Management

Professional Experience

Store Manager

Stripes Clothing, Reno, NV | July 2016-Present

- Controlled costs by negotiating with suppliers
- Hired, recruited, and trained quality employees
- Developed a range of incentive programs to motivate employees (47 employees)
- Successfully marketed clothing to a diverse group of people from college students to mom groups
- Organized Christmas parties and team building events annually
- Ensured compliance with health and safety regulations
- Achieved increased financial performance by 10% for the past three years
- Maintained and organized financial records

Store Manager

Millers Grocery Store, Carson City, NV | September 2012 -June 2016

- Implemented new and innovative promotions to increase store revenue
- Sourced new products that appealed to the customer base
- Handled all payroll and bookkeeping functions
- Managed a successful store with over 20 employees
- Hired, recruited, and trained new employees

Store Manager

Computer Supplies and Technology, Carson City, NV | September 2010 - August 2012

- Increased profitability for two years in a row
- Organized a successful Christmas party each year to thank employees
- Expanded product lines
- Hired, recruited, and trained employees